You cheating bastard!
What?
You're the worst! Apologize to your wife!
I didn't do it.
I did not have an affair.
That article is a complete lie.
Jin Ichijo.
Surrounded by young girls
on a harem vacation
in the middle of a major scandal…
Are you leaving already?
Something has been bothering me.
Enough!
Stop looking at the Internet.
It's so delicious.
Shall we drink?
Vacation is the best!
Just how angry is your wife?
A scorned woman's revenge is terrifying.
What? Who is it?
Who is it?!
Who might you be?
I am…
Jin Ichijo's wife.
Is…
my husband here?
All set.
Here you go.
To think his wife would come here…
How did she even find this place?
Maybe she put a GPS tracker on him?
What? You mean he was cheating
all over with a GPS attached to him?
Old-school actors are like that,
didn't you know?
What are we going to do?
This will be a bloodbath.
This is a compote made from
the summer oranges in our garden.
Please try it.
Midori, when did you make this?
I think I made it yesterday while drunk.
I don't really remember.
It's good.
So you can pick summer oranges
in the garden…
What a wonderful villa.
Thank you.
This villa was left behind
by my grandmother.
We thought we could spend the summer here.
That's right. We all happen to be
unemployed right now.
It's what you would call
a vacation from life!
Vacation…
You too. You came here…
to take a vacation, didn't you?
No, it's not like that.
I just wanted to escape from the media.
What are you trying to do?
Human issues have nothing
to do with us, right?
Sea God.
SEA GOD
It's best not to stick your nose
into human affairs.
You…
do you know who that man really is?
Weekly Shuubun.
A magazine that makes money
week after week off celebrity scandals.
Humans all have secrets, after all.
They expose those secrets
to make a profit.
Sometimes, they even end up
taking people's lives.
They're basically like demons.
Though, saying that
to a Grim Reaper is a bit strange.
Yes.
Ryoko.
I have truly caused you so much trouble.
I'm at your mercy!
I am so sorry!
He's groveling!
The poor wife! This is just too painful.
If it's come to this, she should just get
a big payout and divorce him.
The wife is crying.
This situation is terrible.
Konta.
-What?
-Are we doing a barbecue tonight?
-Will his wife want some?
-Are you stupid?
This is no time for that! As Rinrin said,
a scorned woman's revenge is terrifying!
Mr. Jin may just get stabbed!
-Maybe we should hide the kitchen knives.
-Maybe.
I…
I'm so ashamed.
At this age, to be humiliated like this…
This is hell.
A living hell!
I'm at fault.
I am at your mercy!
I didn't think I would be caught
by Shuubun, hugging on the street.
And it wasn't…
just once, you know!
It was three times!
That hurts.
Three times!
Why didn't you notice?
Your guard was way too low! Idiot!
Ryoko, I am at your mercy!
I am so sorry!
Idiot.
Idiot!
-Idiot!
-I'm sorry!
-Idiot! Don't run!
What should we do?
Let's hide the knives!
Let's hide everything
that could be used as a weapon.
Hide them! What is there?
Should we hide this too?
Hey! You look like a serial killer!
The wife might have brought
a weapon with her.
-Let's take away her bag!
-The bag!
You absolute fool!
Idiot!
You! You absolute idiot!
Okay!
Idiot!
-Check if there's a weapon inside!
-Yes!
Okay!
What is this?
Yes.
The second article
will be a hit with this, Chief Editor.
The cheating piece of trash
Jin Ichijo shows no remorse!
Gathering gyaru at a Tatsumi Town villa
for a harem drinking party!
Let's hit him hard this week too!
Let's keep the fire going!
-Do you enjoy lighting fires?
-Whoa!
What the hell?
Oh, you're the guy from before…
What?
Are you one of Jin Ichijo's
actor buddies or something?
Huh?
I, too, like to set things on fire.
What?
Hot, that's hot!
So hot! It's burning!
Why? So hot!
Why?
So hot!
-Is it on fire?
-So hot!
-Well then, let's put it out.
Nice underhand throw!
Wait, no. Bad, that's bad.
What did you do?
Why did you throw it?
Why did you throw my camera?
Who the hell are you working for?
Just what are you?
I'm the same breed as you guys.
Oh, it's so cute!
You're like an idol.
Where did you buy this, ma'am?
-I want one too.
-Go on!
Did you rummage through my bag?
This is yours, isn't it, ma'am?
No! Um…
Was it in there?
No, I have no intention of using it.
It's just, you know, just in case…
You never know what might happen, right?
What do you mean "just in case"?
What case?
-By just in case, I mean…
-There's other stuff too!
-Stop it!
-Stop it! Don't look!
This…
Wait, so those photos…
They were all you, ma'am?
Seriously?
No! Stop it!
We're busted!
Stop it!
-Ryoko!
-Darling!
Ryoko!
Yes!
What do you like?
Chocolate mint, but more than that…
I like you!
T-This means…
To spice up their marriage,
the wife dressed up and role-played
as different types of women.
And they were
going on dates out in the city?
Then they got photographed?
Then you should just tell everyone that!
You weren't cheating with several women,
it was all your wife!
How could I possibly say that?
Making my wife, at this age,
do all kinds of cosplay
and wander around the city…
If her parents or our relatives
found out about that, we…
we would both die of embarrassment!
That's one "we" too many, darling.
That's not true at all!
It's a wonderful thing!
You two want to date
while keeping things fresh,
just like when you were young.
That means you're putting effort
into your marriage!
That's right, it's lovely!
That is what true love is.
You're the ideal couple!
If you can liven things up
with idol cosplay,
do it as much as you want!
Jin, let's announce this to the world.
Prove to your sponsors
and the film industry
that you weren't four-timing anyone!
Okay.
What a great couple!
-What are you doing?
-You look great together.
Mr. Jin, ma'am,
let's tell everyone the truth.
Everyone?
What is it?
What the hell do you want?
No!
Hold on!
Hey! Hold on! Help me!
It's better than going to hell, right?
Come on!
Help me! Wait!
Help!
No!
Help me! Hey! Wait!
Hey! Come back!
I guess I should report this
to the higher-ups.
I've got this, calm down.
Like this?
Is it rolling already?
It has started.
Well, um…
regarding the recent incident
that's causing a stir,
I, Jin Ichijo, and my wife,
would like to talk about it.
I am so sorry that my husband
was suspected of cheating,
and it caused quite a ruckus.
You see, the truth is,
all of those women were me.
I asked my wife to do cosplay,
and we went out on dates together.
So, this wasn't an affair.
We are husband and wife.
-Yes. We're very sorry.
-We're very sorry.
We apologize for the commotion.
Now, this is the correct way
to use the Internet!
Everyone is being so supportive!
Oh, we just got a Super Chat.
Look.
They're saying,
"You're a wonderful couple."
"Sorry for the misunderstanding."
Wow, goodness…
I'm so happy.
-How kind. Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
And, this broadcast was brought to you
by the next big thing, Konta Hoshino!
The light is too close!
Brought to you by…
-Hey now!
-I'm sorry!
Too close!
You're in the shot.
How lovely.
They're a great couple, aren't they?
Even if they go a bit overboard.
Going overboard is fine.
I want to get married too.
Get married and be a lovey-dovey
couple forever, just like them!
Exactly.
We're on a hard-earned vacation,
so we've got to find some romance.
We can't just be drinking stupid booze
and getting wasted every time.
Romance, huh.
Midori, you seriously
need to get a boyfriend soon!
Not having dated a guy at your age
is honestly a red flag!
Let's invite some guys over
and have a mixer at this villa!
What?
A mixer at the villa…
That sounds just like
a reality show. I love it.
A reality show?
Like a dating show?
I hate that, no way!
-No.
-But, wait…
Mr. Nishigami. I wonder where he went.
I wonder if I'm even capable
of falling in love.
So today is…
Yes! It’s a girls' day.
-Well then…
-Oh, wait…
I wonder where everyone meets
their soulmates.
The new season of Last Princess
is streaming!
All right, let’s watch it! Right now!
I'm in the mood for romance,
so we are watching this now!
I'm Kotaro Komiyama.
This guy seems super shady.
I'm 27 years old.
I'm a cheerleader.
I'm attending a training school.
It’s clout chasing.
I bet it's scripted.
Midori! If you talk like that,
you can't enjoy dating shows!
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.